&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以我们的工作就是清理这场油漆风暴。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
our job is to clean up this paint storm.
所以我们讨论了一下方法，然后我把你们都放在
So we kinda talked a little bit about
the approach before I cut you all loose to
试试看。
give it a shot.
也就是说，我们有一个CSS类，我们有一个转换，
Which is, we have a CSS class,
we have a transition,
我们有所有基本的移动部件，对吧？
we have all the basic moving pieces,
right?
我们能做的最简单的事情就是去掉一些jQuery，然后继续
The easiest thing we can do is get rid of
some of this jQuery and we'll go ahead and
我们会拿到盒子的。
we'll get our hands on the box.
我的意思是，我可以在jQuery中做这部分，我选择不做，
I mean, I could do this part in jQuery,
I'm choosing not to,
没问题。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
it's fine.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
我们会抓住箱子的班级。
we'll grab the class of box.
我们在这里做的第一步是我们可以说
And step one that we do
here is we could just say
box.addEventListener(‘click’)。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
box.addEventListener('click').
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
我们可以说box.classList，
we can say box.classList,
我会用一个开关。
I'll go with a toggle.
我认为，在这种情况下，或者谷歌，或者GOGLE。
I think, or Google, or
goggle in that case.
是啊，你不是都很熟悉吗
Yeah, are you not all familiar with
护目镜的方法？
the goggle method?
&gt；&gt；[笑]&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：好的。
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Okay.
[笑]我们将切换移动类。
[LAUGH] We'll toggle the move class.
是的，我们不会得到我们自己的层和所有类似的东西，但是
Right, and we won't get our own layer and
everything like that, but
这是个好的开始。
it's a good start.
我们最终会得到我们自己的一层，它只是会在同一时间发生。
We will eventually get our own layer,
it's just gonna happen at the same time.
我们去看看吧。
Let's go take a look.
我会在这种情况下做油漆闪光，这样你就可以看到它闪光了。
I'm gonna do the paint flashing in
this case, so you can see It flashes.
它在没有绿色痕迹的情况下移动，并且
It moves without having that
trail of green behind it, and
然后它再次下降。
then it goes back down again.
您可以看到油漆闪光灯VCR处于活动状态
You can see the paint
flash VCR is actively
移动到它自己的层，对吗？
getting moved to it's own layer, right?
它上升到它自己的一层，然后它移动，然后它又下降，
It's going up to it's own layer, then
it's moving, then it's going back down,
因为过渡不再存在。
cuz the transition is no longer there.
但如果我不需要同时做这件事，那就太好了。
But it would be great if I didn't
have to do that simultaneously.
让我们也做一个录音非常快。
Let's also just do a recording real quick.
让我们看看这里发生了什么，我要关掉油漆闪光。
Let's see what we've got going on here,
I'm gonna turn off the paint flashing.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：对，你可以看到，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Right, and you can see,
我们有点击事件。
we've got the click event.
这是不对的。
That's not right.
有趣的事实是直到现在才咬到我，
Fun fact that actually
didn't bite me until now is,
很多时候，如果你在Chrome中有干净的配置文件，你会过得更好。
a lot of times you're better off if
you have clean profile in Chrome.
或者你在隐姓埋名的窗口里做，
Or you do it in an incognito window,
因为有时候你会得到一些你的Chrome扩展
because sometimes you will get some of
your Chrome extension that are also
自言自语。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：酷，所以
interjecting themselves.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Cool, so
我们有事件侦听器。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
we have the event listener.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
它好像在移动。
it kind of moves across.
但有一件事我想让你们首先注意，就是记得我给你们看的时候
But the one thing I want you to notice
first, is remember when I showed you all
在我们做jQuery的时候在那里的那些中间帧？
of those intermediate frames in
there when we did the jQuery one?
他们走了，对吧，因为是的，我们增加了一门课。
They're gone, right,
cuz yeah, we added a class.
合成器线程都是关于移动的，我们基本上是沿着这一层滑动，
The compositor thread is all about moving,
we're basically sliding that layer along,
然后再把它推回去。
and then pushing it back down again.
但我们实际上不再需要在主线程上手动移动它了。
But we don't actually need to manually
move it on the main thread anymore.
所以我们在这里什么都没有发生，这是非常酷的。
So we have nothing happening in here,
which is super cool.
我们可以做得更好一些，比如更复杂的动画或
We could get a little bit better,
like for more complicated animations or
当页面上有很多内容时，
when there is a lot going on the page,
你可以口吃，因为你就像我必须重新粉刷才能得到它自己的层。
you could stutter as you're like I have to
repaint to get it up to it's own layer.
对，那会阻挡一切，
Right, that's gonna block everything,
它会阻止那条线上的其他东西。
it's gonna block other things
going on on that thread.
所以我们可以说，嘿，当你不忙的时候，
So we can say, hey, when you're not busy,
如果你能把它移到它自己的线程上，那就太好了。
if you could move that up to its
own thread, that'd be great.
所以让我们继续
So let's go ahead and
我们会实施的。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以
we'll implement that.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
我们已经有了点击监听器，我们将添加更多的事件。
we've got the click listener,
we're gonna add a few more events.
我们将使用box.addEventListener(‘mouseenter’)。
We'll say
box.addEventListener('mouseenter').
我想之前有人问过，mouseenter和
I think somebody asked earlier,
the difference between mouseenter and
亲爱的。
mousemove.
鼠标爱是有效的每次你悬停在它上面，
Mousemove is effectively every
time you're hovering over it,
mouseenter就像鼠标进入该元素的边界一样。
mouseenter is like when the mouse
enters the bounds of that element.
对，离开就是它离开的时候。
RIght, and leave will be when it leaves.
因为我们不想一直这样做，我们只想第一次做
Cuz we don't wanna do this all the time,
we just wanna do it the first time it
当它离开的时候，第一次想做一些不同的事情。
enters, and the first time wanna to do
something different when it leaves.
很酷，所以我们说box.style.will Change=‘transform’。
Cool, and so we'll say
box.style.willChange = 'transform'.
我们会成为这里的好公民，我们会告诉你老鼠什么时候离开。
And we're gonna be good citizens here, and
we're gonna say when the mouse leaves.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：鼠标离开。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: mouseleave.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们将把它重新设置为
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We'll set it back to
在这种情况下，AUTO是默认值。
auto in this case, auto is the default.
也可以将其设置为空字符串。
You could also set it to an empty string.
我们可能稍后会这样做，但我只是将其设置为auto。
We'll probably do that maybe later,
but I'm just going to set it to auto.
很酷，然后当过渡结束时，也是放下它的好时机。
Cool, and then when the transition ends,
that's also a good time to put it down.
所以你可以说，box.addEventListener(‘transftionend’)。
So you could say,
box.addEventListener('transitionend').
CSS转换和
It's really cool that
the CSS transitions and
动画将触发JavaScript事件。
animations will trigger JavaScript events.
所以你知道什么时候过渡或者
So you know when that transition or
动画已经完成了。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：借口
that animation has completed.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Excuse
当我学习打字的时候。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，很酷
me as I learn how to type.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, cool, and
我们会做同样的事。
we'll do the same thing.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：这一次，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And this time,
我要重新打开油漆闪光。
I'm gonna turn back on paint flashing.
你能看到悬停在它上面将它移动到它自己的层上吗？
Can you see hovering over it
moved it to its own layer.
当我的鼠标进入和离开时，它移动了。
When my mouse entered and left, it moved.
当我点击时，那里只有纯GPU动画。
When I click,
it's just pure GPU animation there.
最后一个是我们进行了过渡
That final one was we put
on the transition and
我们想再次被击倒。
that we wanted to be put back down again.
但实际上在主线程上没有发生任何事情
But there's really nothing that
happens on the main thread
当我们在做动画的时候。
as we're doing the animation.
右，这意味着没有其他布局或样式重新计算或JavaScript或
Right, which means no other layouts or
style recalculations or JavaScript or
任何其他正在发生的事情都将停止这种黄油般的平滑动画。
anything else going on is going to
stop that buttery smooth animation.
酷，让我们来看看这层。
Cool, let's actually look
at that in the layers.
如果这里没有图层标签，
And if you don't have
the layers tab up here, again,
您只需转到这三个点，转到更多工具并查找图层，然后
you can just go to these three dots,
go to More Tools and find Layers, and
那么它就会在那里。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
then it will be there.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
然后我喜欢在那里给自己一点旋转，
then I like to give myself just
a little bit of rotation there,
好好享受一下吧。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：往前走，你可以看到，
treat myself to that.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Go ahead you can see,
它在自己的层上，然后又向下。
it's up on its own layer,
and it's back down.
它向上，它向下，我真的可以一整天都这样做，
It's up, it's down, it's up, it's down,
I could literally do that all day,
我会尊重你的时间而不是。
I will respect your time and not.
[笑]但我永远不会停止对此感到有趣和惊讶。
[LAUGH] But I will never cease
to be amused and amazed by that.
好吧，酷，所以我们做到了。
All right, cool, so we did it.
非常有用的一件事即将到来，
Very useful for one thing are about to,
浏览器将处理哪些应该属于它自己的层，哪些不应该。
the browser will handle what deserves
its own layer and what doesn't.
但你可以在听的时候给它推荐，
But you're allowed to give it
recommendations on listen,
我在这里写了JavaScript。
I wrote the JavaScript here.
我知道这里会发生什么，你为什么不做好准备呢？
I know what's about to happen here,
why don't you get ready for it?
在这种情况下，你实际上可以节省很多钱。
And you can actually
save a lot in that case.
是的，因为如果你是动画片的话，
And yeah,
cuz if you're animations are janky,
为什么会有呢？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我可以问一下吗？
why even have them?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Can I ask
一个问题？&gt；&gt；steve kinney：当然。
a question?
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Of course.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：如果你有一个很重的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you have a really heavy
元素页面，在Enter上是否更容易
element page,
would it be easier to just, on enter
将该元素或其中一个元素转换为它的层，将其留在那里？
transform that element, or one of the
elements, to it's layer, leave it there?
不必一直断断续续[CROSSTALK]只是
Instead of having to go on and
off all the time [CROSSTALK] just
有点像拖动鼠标。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：如果
kind of drag your mouse around.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: If it's
会是一件永久性的事情，是的，对，做一些事情。
gonna be a permanent thing like,
yeah, right, doing stuff.
但如果你想大多数事情，如果是这样的话，
But if you think about
most things if it is like,
假设你在偷走东西。
let's say you're swiping things away.
让我们说它就像一个特雷罗，对吧，或者其他类似的东西。
Let's say it's like a Trello, right,
or something along those lines.
是的，你可以推广它，但你可以再次移动它。
Yeah, you can promote it,
but you could move it again.
但随着用户继续使用该应用程序，并且您正在制作越来越多的应用程序
But as the user continues to use that app,
and you're making more and more and
层数越多，成本就越高。
more layers, you run the cost.
主线程和合成器线程有效地共享存储空间，
The main thread and the compositor
thread effectively share memory space,
你可以用完的，对吧？
which you can run out of, right?
所以像侧边栏这样的东西，一般规则应该是，
So stuff like a sidebar,
the general rule should be,
完成后把所有东西都放回去，除非你有真正好的理由。
put everything back when you're done
unless you have a really good reason.
所以他们会一直使用侧边栏，或者菜单，或者
So a sidebar that they're gonna interact
with all the time, or a menu, or
也许，沿着这些路线的某些东西可能是一个例外。
something along those lines
might be an exception, maybe.
但它应该非常明智地使用。
But it should be used like
incredibly judiciously.
因为是的，如果它失去了控制，用户花了很多时间
Because yeah, if it gets out of control
and the user spends a lot of time on
页面，最终你会创建越来越多的层。
the page, eventually you're gonna
create more and more layers.
它会变得越来越成问题
It's gonna become increasingly problematic